Honey,
today is the seventy-sixth,
see if he can show me the price.
man, it's not long now,
see I don't have.
while we're here talking about the event
and i'm trying
negotiate something for this series finale,
I did my 1st face-to-face event and there were only 5 people,
why not try to do 1 last event?
many people sent messages asking.
this face-to-face event is on,
it's 1 opportunity for me to connect with people,
even more so here at the Anchieta post.
that's when I had 1 idea,
pakai daun,
this shovel and this broom
it's from the gas station.
this shed here is not mine either,
it's from the post that I'm living.
Man,
Me sleeping in this shed here,
they give me coffee,
I USE bathroom,
Wi fi and they never asked me for anything in return.
then it's time to reciprocate
100% of the income that the US makes in this face-to-face event.
I will donate 1 Christmas box to the employees
here from this post.
the difference of the face-to-face event is that
if you have any questions about the content
you can take this
directly with me,
plus I do some Hot Six.
if you haven't signed up yet,
there is still time,
send a DM and write
posts Anchieta that I send the payment link.